A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
Maps and flat files
undated
Rockefeller Archive Center
FA465
1 Cubic Feet
Actual extent unknown
Conditions Governing Access note
Retrieval times for maps and flat files may exceed 24 hours. Individual items may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement note
Maps and flat files are arranged in 56 series, according to the archival collection that the material originated from, or by subject matter (when original provenance is not known). Series are further arranged in subseries when applicable.
Series 1: Rockefeller Foundation. Series 2: Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller. Series 3: Rockefeller Family and Associates: Tioga Series. Series 4: Nelson A. Rockefeller papers. Series 5: John D. Rockefeller 3rd. Series 6: Pocantico Hills. Series 7: Hillcrest. Series 8: Rockwood Hall. Series 9: Laurance S. Rockefeller. Series 10: Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records. Series 11: Blanchette H. Rockefeller. Series 12: Sleepy Hollow Restorations/Historic Hudson Valley. Series 13: Rockefeller University. Series 14: Ford Foundation. Series 16: Agricultural Development Council, Inc. Series 17: American Council for Arts in Education. Series 18: China Medical Board, Inc. Series 19: Commonwealth Fund. Series 20: Russell Sage Foundation. Series 21: Archdiocese: Russell Sage Foundation. Series 22: Goldstone and Hinz. Series 23: Grand Teton Lodge Company. Series 24: Hudson Hills Press. Series 25: International Business Economic Corporation (IBEC). Series 26: International Education Board (IEB). Series 27: JY Ranch. Series 28: Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI). Series 29: JDR 3rd Fund. Series 30: Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC). Series 31: Near East Foundation (NEF). Series 32: Population Council. Series 33: Social Science Research Council (SSRC). Series 34: Sealantic Fund. Series 35: Simpson family papers. Series 36: Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University faculty. Series 37: Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University faculty. Series 38: Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial. Series 39: Conrad W. Anner. Series 40: John C. Bugher. Series 41: John R. Camp. Series 42: Kenneth Chorley. Series 43: Harold P. Fabian. Series 44: Charles Burton Fahs. Series 45: Lawrence B. Dunham. Series 46: Paul Ehrlich. Series 47: Lewis W. Hackett. Series 48: John H. Knowles. Series 49: Leopold Koss. Series 50: William M. Myers. Series 51: Leonard Outhwaite. Series 52: Oscar M. Ruebhausen. Series 53. Benjamin E. Washburn. Series 54: Joseph Willits. Series 55: John D. Rockefeller 3rd Associates: Edgar B. Young. Series 56: Hudson Highlands. Series 57: Miscellaneous.
Scope and Contents note
Maps and flat files is an artificial collection created by the RAC in order to efficiently and effectively manage and present the oversized flat materials across all our archival holdings.
This material includes but is not necessarily limited to: architectural drawings, artwork, blueprints, charts, citations, oversized documents, graphs, maps, photographs, posters, publications, renderings, whiteprints, and other such items that necessitate flat storage.
Separated Materials note
The majority of the maps and flat files have been physically separated from an archival collection.
When the specifics of this separation are known, the details are provided either in this finding aid, or writen on a separation sheet physically accompanying the item.
In many cases, the specific details of the provenance are simply unknown.
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1
  - Letter regarding plans of Medical Building and Portion of Post Hall (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Retrieval times for maps and flat files may exceed 24 hours. Individual items may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.
  - "Theater of war in Europe, Africa and Western Asia". smaller maps attached, 1942 July; MAP (Drawer A 1, Folder 1)
  - "Proposed Office Building" (Harrison & Abramowitz, architects), 1957 July 13; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 1)
    General note
    P*R-05*4
  - RF Metal Display Case "file with RF decoration plans", MISCELLANEOUS (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 1)
    P*R-05*3
  - "Proposed AC for R.F. Offices New Delhi" (Volkart Brothers, architects, New Delhi), BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 1)
    P*R-05*2
  - Time & Life Building- Sub Basement & Mezzanine, WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 2)
    P*R-05*7
  - Projection of new Sfondrata Hall, 1962 February 28; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 2)
    P*R-05*11
  - Legenda District Adjibarang, Legenda District Djatilawang, Legenda District Poerwokerto (closed 8/13/35 RF/146 Hydrick p.6 of regency Poerwokerto the Activities of the Unit by the Villages), MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 3)
  - Watercolor sketch "Projection of New Sfondrata Hall" R.F Villa Serbelloni Bellagio Sfondfrata re-building plans, 1961, rev. 1962 February 28; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 1)
    P*R-05*9
  - R.F Villa Serbelloni Bellagio "Sfrondrata Building- Fa'ade, Floor plan of Entire Space, Elevation of Interior Hall" in colored pencil, 1961; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 3, Folder 1)
  - Sfondrata Kitchen, North, East, South, West Elevations and floor plan, (Quantity 5) (Drawer A 3, Folder 1)
    P*R-05 10
  - Rockefeller Foundation Sites around Paris, MAP (Quantity 15) (Drawer A 3, Folder 1)
    P*R-05 1
  - Rough Plan of Dormitory, School of Public Health, (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P-1H T57 #11-15
  - Plans of Medical Building and Portion of Post Hall used for Medical Sciences, (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P-MS AM 3 of 3 #1
  - Layout of Radioisotope Techniques Training Center and Chemical Research Laboratory, (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
  - Insectorium, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P ME-31
  - "12th and 13th floor Chemistry" Quimica, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2). Oversized. (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P-ME 2 #1-2
  - Hygiene Institute, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P ME-1 #1-2
  - Veterinary School, 1958 September 4; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P ME 1-2
  - Library and Proposed Construction, 1956 January; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P ME 2 1
  - UCDSM Bindery & Photographic Unit, 1964 November 21; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P M-2 1
  - Agricultural and "Ganaderia Ministries-Granja Experimental Tibaitata", BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P EL-1
  - Site plan for "University Neurological Clinic, received for 1936 University Hospital Department, NYC", 1934; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    PC 79C-1
  - "Dog Kennel" - Received with letter from Citt Leach, 1936 October 7; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 9) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    PAL - I 1
    Scope and Contents note
    Letter not included with blueprints
  - "Proposed Addition to Rabies Experimental Lab" - Received with letter from CN Leach to J.A. Ferrell, 1936 October 7; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    PAL - I 10 B-155
  - Dog Lab and Dog cage, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    PA 1-1, 11-12
  - Planta del 3rd Piso, WHITEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P B2 #1-4
  - National Hospital, 1934 November-December; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 9) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
    P-H N-1a-h
  - from University of Pennsylvania Museum "Talek Project". Maps of archaeological site (University of Pennsylvania), 1960; MAP (Quantity 10) (Drawer A 6, Folder 1)
  - Harrison, Lou: Letter to Peggy Rockefeller, 1952 September 11; DOCUMENT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 2)
    File Plan note
    Series 200R
  - Paris Office Files DMDH. (Drawer A 6, Folder 3)
    RG 6.1
  - "The World Needs Nurses, Your Ally Against Enemy Disease" World Health Organization (World Health Organization), POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 3)
    RG 6.2 Series 2
  - 2 World Health Organization newsletters-European program- copy sent to AJW, WHO "Special Issue on Malaria Eradication". (World Health Organization), 1952 July 2; PUBLICATION (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 6, Folder 3)
  - Paris Office Files DMPH General. Russell, Paul (Drawer A 6, Folder 3)
  - Enclosed brochure in envelope: Charles Hayden Memorial Library. (Charles Hayden Memorial Library), PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
    P Ma-1
  - Newspaper Article "Republique Francaise: Universite de Paris- Faculte Des Lettres, Institut D'Etudes Islamiques", 1951 November 20; PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
  - Plans B, 636, 1- Amplacion del edificio de labratoria de la seccion de estudos especiales de Ministero de trabajo hygiene y prevision social planta del 3rd piso cuberta detalles vanos de ventanas, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 9, Folder 1)
  - PLAT MAPS FOR CONSTRUCTION, "FUNDACION PARA LA EDUCACION SUPERIOR - ESCOBAR - HOLQUIN - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL 1960S, 1970S", 1977 March 31; MAP (Quantity 46) (Drawer A 12, Folder 6)
    RF 1.7 (A81) PROJECT FILES, SUBSERIES 150 (311)
    Separated Materials note
    SEPARATED FROM PAPER COLLECTION. Folder 4693
  - Sveriges Utsadestorening Svalov; Swedish Seed Association, Svalof, Sweden." Elevation and floor plan., 1956 October 18; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 2, Folder 1)
  - Plot plan: "County Hospital of Turku, Ground Plan of the Site." Plot plan of buildings including photographs., 1947 July 11; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 2, Folder 1)
  - "Hebrew University- Agricultural History." Includes notes for two panoramas- "Reconstructed Shivta Farm- summer 1959" & "Avdath Farm", 1960; PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 4) (Drawer D 2, Folder 1)
    825D
  - Science photomontage: "100 Photomontage. Used in PR 1940 front page.", MISCELLANEOUS (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer D 2, Folder 1)
    21737
  - set of 11 canvas-backed charts on Hookworm campaign, with accompanying documents from lecture, 1923; GRAPH (Quantity 11) (Drawer H 4, Folder 1)
  - Cox and Reece Investigations: photostats of newspaper articles relating to case, PRINT (Drawer J 5)
  - poster for JAMFEST: World Youth Festival of the Arts 1985 in Kingston Jamaica (original poster art by Tom McMullen), 1985 April; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 1)
  - organizational chart for the Ethiopian Ministry of Agriculture, 1970; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 1)
  - plans of Social Sciences library at National University of Zaire, 1973 April 6; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 1)
  - plans, facades, and coupes from Universite National du Zaire (staff housing), 1973 May 3; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 1)
  - posters and charts from the Departamento Nacional de Saude Publica, GRAPH (Quantity 5) (Drawer J 4, Folder 1)
  - 2 blueprints from Baghdad, "Royal Hospital" and "Medical School" (Government Architect), 1927 February 21 and April 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer J 3, Folder 2)
    80
  - explanatory chart listing members of various Rockefeller-related boards (GEB, CMB, etc), post-1914; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 3)
    marked on reverse "17", "903 Members & Meetings 1915?", "copy attached to 1923 March 1"
  - building plan of 32nd Floor (of RCA Building?), ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 3)
  - Maps: Untitled, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 25+) (Drawer Q 4, Folder 6-Jan)
    RG 1.6 Projects
    Separated from paper collection.
  - International, 1/100
    - "A Fortune Map, Atlantic and Pacific Arenas and World Island" (Time Magazine), 1942; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 1, Folder 4)
      M-P 100 W90-1-3
    - Map "Great Circle Airways" Map of Air Traffic Over Arctic Circle, Time Magazine, May 1943, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 4)
      M-P 100 W91
    - World map (Rand McNally), c. 1950; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 3, Folder 2)
      M-P 100 W 96
    - War Relief Projects: Belgium: Embroidered flour sack, MISCELLANEOUS (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 5, Folder 1)
    - World Map, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer R 3, Folder 4)
      M-P 100 W94
  - United States, 1/200
    - Western Hemisphere Defense Map (U.S defense map on back), 1941 December 8; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 4)
      M-P 200 Un 3e
    - United States areas and Municipalities Closed or Open to Travel by Certain Soviet citizens as of Jan. 6, 1961. Eastern & Western Halves., 1961 January 6; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 2)
      M-P 200 Un-4a&b
    - Wildlife Reserve: Bird Refuge, 1912-1913; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 6, Folder 3)
      1.1 Series 200 folder 141
    - Lincoln Center for Performing Arts spiral- Bound Book (Lincoln Center), PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      P*L-5*a Series 200R Lincoln Center
    - American Council of Learned Sor.- Encyclopedia of Islam EFD to JM/CBF/MEN, 1957 December 1; (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      RG 1.2 200R
      Custodial History note
      File appears to be missing from collection.
    - "Nature Conservation Demonstration Area," National Headquarters- Boy Scouts of America. (Boy Scouts of America), 1959 August 7; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200D
    - "Generalized Map of Soil Erosion in the United States" (Soil Conservation Service), 1948 July; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
    - Columbia University Human Reproduction Dept. Plans for Levels A-D of proposed building., 1970 December 29; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200A
    - "Vacant Properties in East Harlem" & "East Harlem Planning Studio- Vest Pocket Park Project at 110th St." (3) Columbia University Harlem Planning (Columbia University Harlem Planning), 1968 April; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      1.2 Series 200
    - Photocopy of Photographic plate and negative: "Anthropoid Experiment Station for Yale University in Orange Park, Florida.", 1929 November 6; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      Series 200 F 66 #6
    - Set of 3 postcard-sized drawings and photograph of proposed University of Missouri Biochemistry building. Received with letter from W.C. Curtis to F.B. Hansen (W.C. Curtis), 1939 October 16; RENDERING (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      P M69 Series 200
    - Map in colored pencil: "Hispanic America, Map No. 2.", MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      RG 1.2 200S
    - Spiral-bound booklet: "Tuberculosis Hospital Plans.", PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      P-H*A-2*1-7
    - Small booklet of blueprints of Medical Center NY, NY (Columbia University)- HW/EB/E. Hall (Columbia University), BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200 P-MS, C63, 1-59
    - The Johns Hopkins Medical Institutions Building Locations., 1957 January 18; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3); creased. (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200 P-MS J1
    - Set of 9 photostat charts: RF Support for SSRC. Includes original envelope., 1924-1952; GRAPH (Quantity 9) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200 C-1 1-9
    - Small spiral-bound booklet of architectural plans: "A Medical Research Building for The Dartmouth Medical School.", PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200 P-MS D1
    - Set of 7 postcard-sized, photocopied architectural drawings: "The Henry Phipps Psychiatric Clinic, The Johns Hopkins Hospital, Baltimore.", 1913; RENDERING (Quantity 7) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      P-H J 621
    - Service of the Albany Medical College to Communities of Its District." Used in docket meeting 1928 November 5th., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200 P-MS A21
    - Lincoln Center Site Plan, 1959 July 16; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      PL-5e 200R
    - Brown University- Building & Grounds Dept., 1946 June 15; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200 P Br-1
    - Radiation Laboratory- Physics Dept., University of California: 184-inch Cyclotron., 1939-1940; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200 P C13
    - 2 blueprints (original and negative). Laboratories for the study of Influenza and State Dept. of Health. Berkeley, CA., 1937-1938; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      P C13 and C13a
    - Site Plan- Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts., 1956 October 25; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200R PL-5b
    - Cornell University Medical College (2 items) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      P C80 1 and 2
    - The Yale Anthropoid Experiment Station near Orange Park, Florida., 1929 November 8; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 7) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      200P F66 1-7
    - National Cultural Center, National Capital Planning Commission." Enclosed with letter from R.L. Stevens to J.G. Harrar., 1963 September 9; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 4)
      P N-5 200R
    - "Standard Wood Parts for Iron Frame Master Construction." (Lord & Burnham Greenhouse Designers), 1948 January 21; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      Series 200 P B1 #3
    - Farm Crops Greenhouse for Ministerio Agricultura y Ganaderia, Bogota, Columbia., 1951 July 19; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      Series 200 P B1 #4-7
    - Haverford College, Isaac Sharpless Hall- Biology Department." Ground floor through 4th floor plans., 1960 June 1; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 5) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
    - Diagram of Van Der Graaf Generator (U. of Missouri), received with excerpt of Warren Weaver diary, 1937 November 3; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      PM 66
    - "Biochemistry Building, University of Missouri." Floor plans & elevations of main building and plan of greenhouse., 1939 July 24; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      200
      includes smaller map of campus attached to sheet # 3
    - Proposed Development for Stanford Memorial Hall and Outdoor Auditorium., 1936 January; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1). Oversized.; folded. (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      Series 200 Pt-1 no. 6
    - "Laboratories of Epidemiology & Public Health at the Yale Medical School." 6th-8th floor plans. (Douglas Orr & Philip Johnson, Architects), 1961 November 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      Series 200 P R-L 3
    - "Plan of 5th floor, new laboratory complex, University of Pennsylvania." Include 3 site plans of new botanical and microbiology complex. (University of Pennsylvania), BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      Series 200 P P-60 1
    - Laboratory Building, N.Y. Botanical Garden. 1st & 2nd floor plans., WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      P-NY 1
    - Preliminary Program, Oceanographic Building, University of Washington." 1st-3rd & roof floor plans., 1931 March 3; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      P-W27 1-4
    - Main Floor Plan, Stanford Memorial Hall." Received with smaller plans in letter from L.E. Bassett., 1936 February 14; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      P-St-1 1
    - The University of North Carolina, 1936 December 27; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      Series 200 P UNC 1 and 2
    - Playhouse Theatre, Chapel Hill, N.C.: Basement through 2nd floor plans & elevations., 1937; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 7) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      Series 200 P UNC 3-9
    - "Hospital Facilities Section, U.S. Public Health Service." Maternity floor for 100-bed general hospital, Pediatric Unit, Children's Bathroom, Children's Bedroom., 1944; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      P-H M 1-4
    - Oceanographic Laboratory for University of Washington., 1931 July 2; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 21) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      P-W27a #1-21
    - School of Public Health, Ann Arbor, Michigan. Plot & 1st-3rd floor plans., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      P-IH M-1 no. 1-4
    - School of Hygiene & Public Health of the Johns Hopkins University. Basement through 9th floor and Wolfe Street elevation plans., 1923 April 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 11) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      P-IH J62b no. 1-11
  - California, 1/205
    - Chemical-Biology at Californing Istitute of Technology. Listing of departments and faculty., POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 6, Folder 5)
      205d CIT C-1
  - Kentucky, 1/220
    - Flyer with Archival Copy "Hookworms" County Board of Health, Kentucky, 1915, PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 1)
      220H
  - Philippines, 1/242
    - Map of Philippine Islands- Density of Population 1939. Map of Population Research, Princeton., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 3)
      M-P 242 P1
    - booklet of Architectural Drawings "International House," College of Agriculture, University of the Philippines, PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      P P-75 1 (Booklet)
    - Proposed College Theater for Philippine Normal College - First Floor Plan, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      P-72 3
    - Proposed Electrical Plan for Stage Lighting of Arena Theater for Philippine Normal College", ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      242 P-P-72 2
    - Proposed College Theater for Philippine Normal College, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      P P-72 1
    - Exchange Faculty Housing at the University of the Philippines, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      242 P P-78 16
    - Ground, Second, and Third Floor Plans, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      P71 4 2-4
    - drawing of Business School "University of Philippines- Business School", 1957 December 9; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      242 P P-71 1
    - College of Agriculture- Central Experiment Station; University of the Philippines, 1933 July 15; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      P-77 8b
    - Proposed Economic Development Building- University of the Philippines, with correspondence, 1957 August 5; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      242 P P-70 1-4
    - Blueprint negatives "Proposed Arena Theater Philippine Normal College", undated; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      P P-72 4-7
    - U.P. College IRRI Site, 1962 April 23; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      242 P P-77 8a
    - organizational charts: "Key to Philippines Anopheles" Adults and Larvae for the malaria investigations unit, international health department, 1934; GRAPH (Quantity 2). Oversized. (Drawer A 7, Folder 3)
      242 C8
    - Guesthouse, Pavilion, Bathhouse, Filter and Swimming Pool, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
      P P-77 3x-y
    - Photocopy of a sketch, "Swimming Pool and Pavilion,", RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
      P P-77 3T
    - Philippine Islands, International Rice Research Institute-1960 December Meeting, (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
    - International Rice Research Institute, Los Banos, Philippines. A.J Luz Associates, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
    - B&W photocopy of drawing: "Guest House/Alternative Scheme", WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
      P P-77 3 s
    - B&W photographs of architectural models of Rice Research Institute, PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
    - watercolor paintings- "Guache Architectural." Guest House, Director's Residence, Staff House, & 8-Family Apartments., RENDERING (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
      P P-77 3O, 3P, 3R, 3Q
    - large gouache watercolor sketch- "Main Entrance-IRRI staff housing, Los Banos.", RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
      P P-77 3E
    - large gouache watercolor sketch- "IRRI Staff Housing Scheme "B"-Los Banos, Laguna.", RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
      P P-77 3H
    - large gouache watercolor sketch- "IRRI Staff Housing Scheme "A"- Los Banos, Laguna.", RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 7, Folder 4)
      P P-77 3B